

About Me

Francis Jay Rotol is a diligent IT professional working in a theme park setting. He is focused on achieving success through his expertise and dedication to his role.

Contact

- 09512352816
- rotoljay03@gmail.com
- Villalimpia Loay, Bohol

🏠 Skills

- Tech-Support
- Can do office work
- Problem Solving Skill
- LEADERSHIP SKILL
- CAN WORK UNDER PRESSURE

AX Language

- English
- Filipino

Francis Jay D Rotol

IT Tech-Support

Education

(2011 - 2015)

HOLY TRINITY ACADEMY OF LOAY

ICT

3.65

(2021-2024)

CITE

COMP E

3.74

Experience

(2023 - 2024)

OJT AT ANJOWORLD THEME PARK

anjoworld global sourcing inc

- create more than 100 graphic designs for big companies
- complete a lot of complicated work

(2017 - 2019)

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

larana, inc

- create more than 100 graphic designs for big companies
- complete a lot of complicated work